还记得你16岁的时候刚来我家
Remember what I told you when you were 16
我跟你说的话吗
and you first came to live at my house?
永远不要忘记  我爱你
Never forget I love you.
他和他的妻子把我收留了
Him and his wife took me in.
他们拯救了我
They saved me.
你一旦拉起引线
You go pulling a thread,
谁也不好说什么会被揭露出来
there's no telling what all unravels.
你不想知道发生了什么吗
Don't you want to know what happened?
我对我做的事并不后悔
I do not regret what I did here.
我要向艾琳求婚
I'm gonna ask Erin to marry me.
每次她都陪着我
She's been there for me,
我想陪着她
and I want to be there for her.
我是联调局特工詹尼弗·斯宾塞
I'm FBI Special Agent Jennifer Spencer.
来这里为你提供一份工作
I'm here with a job offer.
他们找我  让我去纽约
They want me in New York.
你知道这件事
You know about this.
我知道我需要想办法
Well, I knew I needed to do something.
不要回头
Don't look back.
事实上  我也不知道我是怎么想的
The truth is, I'm not really sure how I feel about it.
我...
I'm...
我不是很擅长这种东西
I'm not really good at that stuff,
你懂的
though, you know,
表达感情什么的
expressing feelings.
我知道我别无选择
I know I had no choice.
她必须走
I mean, she had to go.
所以
So...
那样的话  我并不后悔我所做的事
in that sense, I don't really regret what I did.
只不过...
Just...
我是说  现在她真的走了
I mean, now that she's really gone,
我感觉...
I'm just feeling...
孤独
Lonely?
是的
Yeah.
她就像我女儿
She was like a daughter to me.
会很艰难
It's gonna be tough.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
真的很艰难
Really tough.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋
不好意思
I'm sorry.
翻译     H小欠   Lynn_宁   圈圈   pang
校对     圈圈
我得走了
I gotta go.
时间轴     西查   大葱
枪贩子是印第安纳州外的两个骑行客
The gun dealers are two bikers out of Indiana.
买家是跟南部老鹰有关系的帮派成员
Buyers are gangbangers associated with Southside Hawks.
后期     8T
我们还不知道名字
We don't have any names yet.
交易在老神学院进行
Uh, deal's going down inside the old seminary.
总监     圈圈
那里已经废弃了五年
It's been abandoned for five years.
邻近的两幢楼也早已废弃
Two adjacent buildings are abandoned as well.
我们进去后
Once we're inside,
埃尔和我从西边进去
Al and I are gonna enter here from the west.
鲁塞克  你和阿特沃特从这边进去
Ruzek, you and Atwater going in here.
厄普顿和霍斯特德  你们从这里进去
Upton and Halstead, you go in this way.
警长
Sarge...
西翼有情况
we have got movement on the west side.
一名白人男性  一名西班牙裔男性
One male, white. One male, Hispanic.
均中等身高  体重150左右
Both 5'10" To 6,' about 170 pounds,
有纹身  拿着大行李袋
tatted up, carrying large duffle bags.
刚从一辆黑色的车上下来
They just got out of a black SUV with--
是印第安纳牌照的
with Indiana tags.
收到  我们出发
Copy that. Here we go.
呼叫指挥中心  有人向警方开枪
10-1, 10-1. Shots fired at police.
西亚契街4533号
4533 West Archer.
-准备好了吗  准备好了吗  -嗯
- You ready? You ready? - Yeah.
警察
Police!
快走
Go! Move!
-我去追那些人  -快去
- I got these guys. - All right. Go.
-我去找杰  -收到
- I'm going to find Jay. - Copy that.
芝加哥警察  放下武器
CPD! Drop your weapon!
让开  让开
Out of the way! Get out of the way!
让开
Get out of the way!
我是G5021  我正在交火
This is 5021 George, I'm taking heavy fire.
两名平民在大楼后北边小巷中受伤
I got two civilians down in the north alley behind the building.
我是汉克·博伊特警长
This is sergeant Hank Voight.
-建议封锁附近两个街区  -收到
- Advise responding to shut down a two-block radius. - Copy that.
-我们会封锁两个...  -救命  救命
- We'll set up a two-block... - Help! Help!
有多名持枪袭击者
We have multiple armed offenders.
一定要格外小心
Approach with extreme caution.
-怎么回事  -我不知道  我只听到哭声
- What happened? - I don't know. I heard crying.
赶紧带这些孩子去西边出口
Get these kids out the west exit right now. Now!
好了  我来叫救护车
All right, I'm gonna call an ambulance.
我们没时间了  开你的车
We don't have time. Get your car.
我去前面和你汇合
I'm gonna meet you up front.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第一集
她情况不好
She's in bad shape.
但我们正在尽全力抢救
But we're doing everything we can.
可能性多大
What are the odds?
我说了  我们正在尽全力
Like I said, we're doing everything we can.
我们知道  另外两名伤者呢
We know. What about the other two victims?
-他们怎么样  -跟我来
- Are they okay? - Walk with me.
詹姆斯·佩尔  子弹划伤了他的腿
James Pell, the bullet grazed his leg.
他没事  我们只要填完一些表格就好了
He's fine; we're just finishing up some paperwork.
另一名伤者呢
Hey, what about the other victim?
她没撑住  到医院时已经死了
She didn't make it. Dead on arrival.
我还要签什么文件还是可以走了
I gotta sign the papers, or can I go now?
别着急
Just sit tight.
佩尔先生  我们想和你谈谈
Mr. Pell, we'd like to talk to you
今天刚刚发生的事
about what happened earlier today.
我腿上中枪了  就是这么回事
I got shot in the leg, that's what happened.
你看到打你的那个人了吗
Did you see the men who shot you?
-没有  -一眼都没看到吗
- No. - Not even a quick glimpse?
警官  我刚卷入一起严重的事故
Look, Officer, I was just involved in a traumatic incident.
我现在还处于惊吓之中
I'm still in a state of shock.
拜托别再问我问题了
So, please, no more questions.
好的
All right.
我们会查你的联系信息
We'll get your contact information.
稍后会联络你
Call you later on.
好  现在有三名枪击受害者
Okay, we have three gunshot victims:
一名黑人女性  二十多岁  送往医院途中死亡
female, black, 20s, dead on arrival.
一名叫詹姆斯·佩尔的二十多岁黑人男性
Male, black, mid-20s, named James Pell,
已经出院
treated and released.
子弹只是擦伤了他的腿
The bullet just grazed his leg.
还有一名八岁左右的女孩
And a little girl around eight.
她仍处于危险之中
She's in critical condition.
那个出院的人  我们找他谈过了吗
All right, the guy who got nicked, we talk to him?
找过了  他不是很配合
We tried. He wasn't too cooperative.
声称自己仍处于惊吓之中
He claims he's still in shock.
那些孩子为什么会在那里
And what are those kids doing there in the first place?
那幢楼原来是
It turns out the building was used
一家私人日托中心
as an off-the-books day care center.
一天十元  附近的人
For ten bucks a day, someone in the neighborhood
会帮忙照看你的孩子
will watch your kid.
老大  两名在现场被射杀的帮派成员
Boss, two bikers killed at the scene.
一个名叫安东尼·乔纳斯  24岁
One was Anthony Jonas, 24.
另一个名叫麦克·斯考拉  26岁
Other Mike Scola, 26.
都来自印第安纳州加里
Both from Gary, Indiana.
他们都是石像鬼王的人
And they're both affiliated with the Gargoyle Kings.
你的线人和我们说过这个骑行帮派
That's the biker gang your CI told us about.
好的  出去找你的线人谈谈
All right, hit the streets. Talk to your CIs.
我们来抓出这些凶犯
Let's find these shooters.
-汉克  有时间吗  -什么事
- Hank, got a sec? - Yeah.
你的人现在上新闻了
Your team's all over the news.
你是说今早的事
You talking about the thing this morning?
路人一死两伤
Three innocents hit, one dead?
我们端掉一个非法枪市  嫌犯开火了
We're taking down a gun deal. The suspects opened fire.
独立审查员会仔细审查这个案子的
The independent auditor will be reviewing this incident.
独立审查员
Independent auditor?
改革新政的一部分
Part of the new reform package.
又见面了  汉克
Nice to see you, Hank.
丹尼
Denny.
市长刚刚正式任命了
Mayor just made it official.
丹尼就是独立审查员
Denny's the independent auditor.
能不能让我们叙叙旧
You wanna give us a couple minutes to catch up?
-当然  -多谢  局长
- Sure. - Thank you, Chief.
已经过去多久了  半年了吗
So it's been, what, six months?
差不多吧
Yeah, something like that.
他们总算看了我的档案
Well, they finally looked into my file
意识到我其实是个好警察
and realized I'm a good cop.
而唯一有疑点的案子  鲁法洛谋杀案
And the only case in question, the Ruffalo thing,
已经没事了
it just went away.
现在他们让我来监督整个芝加哥警署
And now they've got me overseeing the whole Chicago PD.
独立审查员
Independent auditor.
搞得我好像是个会计似的
Makes me sound like somewhat of a, uh--an accountant.
更像是法官
more like a judge.
汉克  我只想说  过去的事
Hank, I just want to say that, uh, the past...
就过去了
is the past.
我们之间的那些个破事
All that nonsense that happened between us...
到此为止
It's over.
那就好
That's good to know.
见到你很高兴  汉克
Be seeing you, Hank.
怎么回事  他是谁
Hey, what's going on? Who is this?
他是来给审讯室安装摄像头的
He's here to install cameras in the interrogation room.
主管直接下的令
Direct order from the superintendent.
肯定是那位新来的
Yeah, after his new
独立审查员给他出的主意
independent auditor gave him the idea.
不管是谁  他们都要求今天就装上
Well, whoever it was, they want it done today.
左手边第一间就是
First hall on your left.
要不是我一向率性乐观
If I wasn't so doe-eyed and optimistic,
我会觉得上头对我们不信任了
I'd say we have a trust issue on our hands.
不管怎样  我派了20名干警去案发地附近
Anyway, I've got 20 officers on the ground in the vicinity
搜索两名枪手
looking for the two shooters.
我听见消息就通知你
I'll let you know when I hear something.
-多谢  -没事
- Thanks. - Sure.
-有目击者吗  -还没找到
- Any witnesses? - Not yet.
-那孩子们呢  -他们什么都没看到
- What about the kids? - They didn't see anything,
除了那个中枪的小女孩
except that little girl get shot.
那个托儿所开了多久了
How long has the daycare been here?
不知道  还在找她的父母
Don't know. Still looking for the parents.
抱歉  长官
Excuse me, sir.
这里是正在调查中的罪案现场
This is an active crime scene investigation.
调查中  我看见五个条子在喝咖啡
Active? Hell, I see five cops sipping coffee,
两个在抽烟  还有个在吃烤肉三明治
two smoking cigarettes, and one having a roast beef sandwich.
-请退后  -这儿谁指挥  是你吗
- Please step away. - Who's in charge here, you?
我是奥林斯基警探  别让别人进来
I'm Detective Olinsky. Just don't let anybody else in.
我听说有位女士在这里中枪身亡
I heard a woman got shot here and was killed
还有个小女孩重伤
and the little girl's in critical condition.
调查中的案子我们不能评论
We can't comment on the investigation.
这么说是真的了
So it's true, huh?
请你退回线外去  先生
I'm gonna need you to step back, sir.
你为什么不跟我说下案情呢  奥林斯基警探
Why don't you just fill me in, Detective Olinsky?
要不我和您说下吧
Why don't I fill you in?
两个帮派分子朝警察开枪
Two gangbangers opened fire on the police.
他们杀了一个年轻女性
They killed a young woman
重伤了一名小女孩
and critically injured a little girl.
-这就是案情  明白了吗  -这样啊
- That's what happened. Okay? - I see.
这么说你认为帮派分子要负责了
So you're gonna put it on the gangbangers, huh?
很明显是这样  先生
Yeah, that seems pretty obvious, sir.
能像你这样
Must be nice--
天真又漂亮  真让人羡慕
to be so naive and beautiful too.
两者兼备真不容易
One hell of a combination.
你再说一遍
Did you just say that?
你说什么你再说一遍
-别嚷嚷  警探  -什么情况
- Excuse me, Officer. - Everything okay?
-你刚说什么  -怎么回事
- What did you say? - Excuse me.
-没事  -你们在说什么呢
- We're fine. - What's going on here?
你的人正在向我汇报情况
Your people were just bringing me up to speed.
普莱斯市议员是老朋友了
Alderman Price is an old friend
也是本地社区的重要人士
and an important member of the community.
我们要找科莫娜·威廉姆斯
we're looking for a Kimona Williams.
她就在后面
She's over there.
科莫娜·威廉姆斯
Kimona Williams?
是我
Yeah?
女士  我们需要和你谈一谈
Ma'am, we need to talk to you for a second.
好吧  这边来
O-okay, um...just...
怎么了  出什么事了
What's the matter? Did something happen--
是你女儿  摩根
It's your daughter, Morgan.
摩根
Morgan?
-她不幸中枪了  -不
- She was shot... - No. No.
就今早的事  在老神学院
At the old seminary this morning.
她还活着  没事的
She's alive. It's okay.
她还好吗
But is she okay?
她正在芝加哥医院接受治疗
She's being treated at Chicago Med right now.
你可以搭我们的车去
We can give you a ride, okay?
谁开的枪  谁打的她
Who did this? Who shot her?
我们还不  还不清楚
We're not--we're not sure.
我们会尽全力找到凶手的
We're gonna do everything in our power to find him.
-我保证  -好  好
- I promise. - Okay. Okay.
来吧  快出发吧
Okay? We should go now.
来
Come on.
抱歉  我刚看见你来电话
sorry. I just got your call.
总算找到了女孩的母亲
Finally located the girl's mother.
关上门
Shut the door.
怎么了
What's up?
我刚刚和弹道检测的人谈过了
I just talked to Ballistics.
击中小女孩的是一发九毫米子弹
The bullet that hit the little girl was a nine-millimeter.
帮派分子用的不是点四五吗
Thought the bangers were firing .45s.
是的
They were.
你是说小女孩是我击中的
You saying I shot that little girl?
发射右面子弹的这把枪
The gun that fired the bullet on the right--
就是击中小女孩的那颗子弹
the one that hit the little girl--
也就是左边这颗子弹的枪
fired the one on the left too.
抱歉  但是枪管不会撒谎
I'm sorry, but gun barrels don't lie.
谢了  莫蒂
Thanks, Morty.
根本说不通
Doesn't make sense.
我被火力压制  就找了掩体
I was under fire, and I took cover...
然后我回击了一枪
And I fired one round,
我亲眼看着对方中枪倒地的
and I watched the offender drop.
然后我径直跑向中枪的女人
And then I ran over to the woman who got shot
然后呼叫了支援
and radioed for help.
好吧
Okay.
我没听见有孩子的动静
I didn't hear any kids.
我也没看见任何孩子
I didn't see any kids.
我也没有随便朝四周乱开枪
I didn't just shoot my gun off in the air.
如果是这样  那你不用担心
If that's what happened, you got nothing to worry about.
回去歇一歇吧  等审查小组给你清白再说
Take some time off till the shooting team clears you.
要审查多久
How long is that gonna take?
可能要花点时间
I mean, it might take a minute or two.
现在不太好搞
Things are tricky right now.
你的意思是我应该担心是吗
Are you saying I need to worry?
我只是说不太好搞
I'm saying things are tricky.
萨米  那条短信很急的样子
Yeah, Sammy, that text message was clutch.
你查到什么了
What you got for us?
今早的枪击案我可能查到了点线索
I might have something on that shoot-out this morning.
我刚给一个年轻的帮派成员缝合了伤口
I just stitched up a young gang member.
下腹有一处枪伤  子弹直接穿了过去
Bullet wound to his lower abdomen, went right through.
你怎么知道那是枪伤的
How'd you know it was a gunshot wound?
拜托  你知道我见过多少枪伤吗
Please. You know how many gunshots I've seen?
我的工作就是把死掉的混混变成童子军
I make a living turning dead bangers into Boy Scouts
好让他们的母亲给他们举办葬礼
so their mothers can give them proper burials.
好吧  大约是什么时候的事
All right, and about what time was this?
大约十点左右
About 10:00 or so.
我来的时候他就等在这里了
He was waiting for me when I got here.
他怎么知道要来找你  萨米
How'd he know to come to you, Sammy?
对他们来说  我的陈尸间比医院要好
For them, my morgue's a lot better than a hospital.
不需要填文书  也没有警察...
No paperwork, no police--
至少他们不知道会有
not to their knowledge, anyway.
你知道他的名字吧
You got a name for me, right?
不知道
No.
他当时并不想公开自己的私人信息
He wasn't exactly in the mood to give out personal details.
但我有记下...他的车牌号
But I did get... A license plate.
-好的  -我会去查的
- Okay. - I'll go run it.
-谢了  萨米  -再见
- Thanks, Sammy. - See you.
你真的喜欢这个人吗
So you really like this guy?
你吃醋了
You jealous?
有一点
Yeah, a little bit.
我等着你逮捕嫌犯的时候能多给我点这个
I expect to see some more of these when you make the arrest.
好了  我们去皇家高塔  知道了吗
Okay, we're going to Royal Towers, okay?
2632号房间
Apartment 2632.
嫌犯为黑人男性
Offender's black male,
身材较瘦  身高大约175  20岁出头
wiry, about 5'9", early 20s.
下腹有一处枪伤
He's got a bullet hole in his abdomen.
知道了吗  你们从侧面包抄
Okay? So y'all take the perimeter.
你们去后面查看情况  我们去敲门
You cover the back, and we got the apartment.
行动
Let's roll.
芝加哥警署  开门
Chicago PD. Open up!
怎么了
Yeah?
你是自己吗  还有别人在里面吗
You all alone? Is there anyone else in there with you?
没  就我自己  你们干嘛...
No, I'm--I'm by myself. But why are you--
好的女士  我们需要进屋
Okay, well, ma'am, we're gonna have to step inside
问您几个问题
and ask you a few questions.
这很重要  明白吗
It's very important, okay?
谢谢  麻烦退后
Thank you. Step back, please.
安全
Clear.
好了  屋里一切正常
All right, we're clear in here, guys.
-收到  -看到了吧
- Copy that. - See?
这里没别人
No one else is here.
你们能不能告诉我到底怎么回事
Can you tell me what the hell is going on?
有一位凶杀案嫌犯
Because an offender wanted for murder
今早开了你的车
was driving your car this morning.
那台车登记的就是这个地址
Car registered to this address.
也许你能解释一下原因
Maybe you can explain.
当然
I sure can.
我的车昨晚被人偷了
My car was stolen last night.
我两个小时前才报了警
I filed the police report literally two hours ago.
案件编号就在这里
Case number's right there.
好的我们明白了  抱歉打扰您
Okay, we understand. Sorry about this.
你不知道今天早晨
You don't know anything about what happened
那所老神学院发生了什么
at the old seminary this morning?
我只听说有人因为警察坏了事
All I heard was, some people got shot
而中了枪
because the police screwed up.
你看他们给这些建筑起的全是高大上的名字
You'll notice how they give these buildings prestigious names.
是啊  皇家高塔
All right, Royal Towers,
王后花园  日落风景
Queen's Gardens, Sunset Vista.
多留心一下
Pay attention, dog.
多搞笑啊
It's hilarious.
你和我在想一样的东西吧
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
抱歉
Excuse me.
我们能和你谈谈吗
Mind if we talk to you?
谈什么
About what?
今天早上老神学院
There was an incident this morning
发生了点事情
at the old seminary.
我什么都不知道
I don't know nothing about that.
好  那你应该不介意
All right, then you shouldn't mind
我们问你几个问题吧
if we ask you a few questions.
我介意  很介意
I should, and I do.
请你站住
Stop walking.
离那个孩子远一点  跪下
Step away from the child. Get on your knees.
把手放在我能看见的地方
Keep your hands where I can see them.
我是无论如何不会下跪的  无论是向谁
I'm not getting on my knees for you or for nobody.
不要把手伸进口袋
Do not reach in your pocket.
手机而已  我想让我儿子把这事录下来
It's a phone. I want my son to record this.
先生  不要把手伸进口袋
Sir, do not reach in your pocket.
不然呢  你会开枪打我
Or what? You gonna shoot me?
为了一部手机在我儿子面前杀死我
Kill me in front of my son over a phone?
我不会再说第二遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
很简单的问题
Simple question.
-你今天有没有中枪  -什么
- Did you get shot today? - What?
回答问题  有还是没有
Answer the question, yes or no.
你今天有没有中枪
Did you get shot today?
-没有  -好的
- No, man. - All right.
把你的衣服掀起来
Just lift up your shirt.
你到底想干嘛...
What the hell are you even--
慢慢地把你的衣服掀起来  就几厘米就行
Lift up your shirt nice and slow, just a few inches.
快点
Come on, man.
我要为这位警官掀起我的衣服了
I'm about to lift my shirt up for this officer.
希望有人能用手机把它录下来
I hope somebody's got a phone to record this.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
没事了  你可以走了
We straight. You're good to go.
抱歉造成这样的误会
Sorry about the misunderstanding.
没事了吧
All right?
没事了吧  小伙子
All right, little man?
我们很抱歉
Sorry about that.
行了吧
All right?
我们现在的公关陷入了巨大危机
We got a PR nightmare on our hands.
本来帮派混混是枪手就已经让我们很难看了
Well, the optics weren't good when the gangbanger
更别说是白人警察了
was the shooter, let alone a white cop.
基于时间限制
Look, given the time constraints,
我们已经尽全力了
we did everything we could.
麻烦你解释一下  你们为何
Help us understand why you were engaged
在一家日托中心附近参与了一场如此危险的行动
in a dangerous operation so close to a day care center.
一家非法日托中心  我们根本都不知道它在那里
An illegal day care center. We had no idea it was there.
可你应该知道
Well, you should have.
你的下属应该了解他们管辖的
Your men need to understand the culture
街区的文化背景
of the neighborhoods they police.
在城里这样的地方很常见
Places like that are common in urban areas.
霍斯特德警探当时被人攻击
Detective Halstead was under attack.
他追到了嫌犯  他就开了一次枪
He drew down on a suspect. He fired one round.
子弹穿过了嫌犯身体
The bullet went through the suspect,
然后穿过了一块木头  击中了那个小女孩
then through a piece of wood, and then hit the little girl.
我跟病理室的人谈了
Well, I talked to ISP.
他们发现了
They got one hit of DNA
击中女孩的子弹上只有一个人的DNA  她的
on the bullet that hit the little girl--hers.
是的  但是子弹还是可能打中罪犯的
Yeah, but it still could have hit the offender.
子弹上很难找到DNA
Bullets don't always collect DNA.
你很清楚  这让我觉得
But you already know that, which tells me--
应该让你觉得
Which tells you
我对此非常严肃认真
we're taking this very seriously.
凯文  你知道
Kev, you know, before--
我只是在那个人和他的孩子面前做我该做的事
that guy and his kid-- I was just doing my job, right?
我在审讯一个嫌疑犯
I'm questioning a murder suspect.
他就在那里双手插兜装逼吗
He's noncompliant, puts his hands in his pockets?
-拜托  -他不是装逼
- Come on. - I mean, he got noncompliant
因为你有一点太激进了  仅此而已
because you were a little belligerent, that's all.
没关系
It's okay.
好吧  你知道吗
All right, well, you know what?
我下次给他一个蓝莓甜筒
Next time, I'm gonna offer him a blueberry scone.
老兄  我
Dog, I--
至少让一个黑人
Look, bottom line is, it's not easy
在一个白人警察面前下跪是很难的
for a black man to get on his knees for a white cop,
尤其是他的儿子在那里
especially with his son right there, so--
那如果他就是犯人呢
What if he was the offender
我还在那里平息事件  追求政治正确
and I'm out there soft-pedaling, being all politically correct,
然后被打两枪  还是你替我抗
and I take two to the chest or you do?
你觉得呢
What then?
我不会让这种事发生的
No, I'm not gonna let that happen.
这种情况下我觉得
In this situation, I think it's better
请求他宽恕总比征求他的许可要好
to ask for forgiveness than permission.
兄弟
Hey, man.
审查那边的谈话怎么样
How'd the interview with the shooting team go?
我不知道  很短
I'm not sure. It was pretty short.
他们没问我太多问题
They didn't ask me too many questions.
好的
Okay.
杰
Jay.
还好吗
How you doing?
我正在尽量保持积极
I'm just trying to stay positive.
我之前去了医院
I was at the hospital earlier,
我兄弟说那个小女孩
and my brother said there's a good chance
-有很大可能  -你没听说吗
- the little girl's gonna be-- - Oh, you didn't hear?
她死了  杰
She died, Jay.
大家都知道了
It's all over the news.
好吧
Okay.
我刚想告诉你
I was just about to call you.
你说她会挺过来的
You said she was gonna make it.
你说她...
You said she was gonna--
我说了有可能  好吗
Hey, I said she had a chance, okay?
她状况太差了  失血过多
She was in bad shape, lost too much blood.
-我知道  -我们已经尽力了
- I know. - There's only so much we can do.
我知道  抱歉  我只是
I know. I'm sorry. I just...
反黑组有什么消息吗
Any luck with the gang unit?
没有  我们调查了很多照片  但是
No. We looked through lots of photos, but...
这些黑帮一定是新入道的
These bangers must be new to this clique.
已经八个小时了  我们还是没有凶手的线索吗
It's been eight hours. We still got no lead on the shooter?
我有一些发现
I got something.
我翻了骑手的手机  看到了两条商量重大行动短信
I dumped the biker's phone, found two texts to a burner
发给了一个一次性手机
discussing a deal for some thumpers.
收信人叫小哥
Recipient's name is Lil GG.
也许是我们要找的凶手之一
May be one of our shooters.
追查一次性手机了吗
Track the burner?
是的  是在距离犯罪现场三个街区的小商店里
Yeah, to a mini mart about three blocks from the crime scene.
好的  你们去
Good. You two.
打扰了
Excuse me.
我们在找在这里买电话的人
Looking for someone who bought a phone here.
外号叫小哥
His nickname's Lil GG.
不知道谁叫这个名字
Don't know anyone with that name.
他和当地一个黑帮很熟悉
Well, he's affiliated with one of the local gangs--
叫南部老鹰
Southside Hawks.
我猜他们买了很多一次性手机
Guessing they buy a lot of burners.
想起谁了吗
Ring any bells?
没有吗  拜托帮帮我
No, nothing? Come on, man, help me out.
我告诉你了  我不认识他们
I told you, I don't know them.
好吧  那我需要调用你的监控摄像了
All right. Well, I'm gonna need your video surveillance.
没必要了
Not necessary.
我弄错了  不是这家店
I screwed up. We're at the wrong store.
不好意思
Sorry for the inconvenience.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还是不要待在这里为好  杰
It's really best if you get out of here, Jay.
他们说我可以坐坐班
I was told I could work desk duty.
警长  小商店里有突破
Sarge, caught a break at the mini mart.
小店主人的妻子知道小哥
The owner's wife knows Lil GG.
他的真名叫凯文·肖
His real name's Calvin Shaw.
找到地址然后拿到搜查令
Get an address and an arrest warrant.
-已经拿到了  -好的
- It's already done. - Good.
-你们和鲁塞克  厄普顿一起去  -好的
- All right, you two go with Ruzek and Upton. - Yep.
我们去会会小哥
Let's pay this Lil GG a visit.
交给我们
We got you.
-回家吧  -好的
- Go home. - Yeah.
警长
Hey, Sarge,
你有琳德赛的消息吗
have you heard from Lindsay?
没有  你呢
Nope. You?
我给她留了言
I left her a message.
还没回我
I didn't hear back.
可能在执行任务
Probably on assignment.
她不会再回来了  是吗
She's not coming back, is she?
听着  她是时候继续向前了
Look, it was time for her to move on.
就是如此
It just was.
你要接受这件事
You need to make peace with it.
-上  -芝加哥警署
- Go. - Chicago PD!
注意楼梯
Stairs!
发现一具尸体
Got a body!
好的  我们来了
All right, crossing.
-安全  -头部中两枪
- Clear. - Got two to the head.
腹部呢
What about the stomach?
死者是凯文·肖  也就是小哥
DOA is Calvin Shaw, AKA Lil GG.
头部中两枪  但是腹部完好
Two bullet wounds to the head, none to the abdomen,
很遗憾  他不是霍斯特德击中的人
so he's not the guy Halstead shot, unfortunately.
看起来是小哥的团伙紧张了
It sounds like Lil GG's partner got nervous.
也许因为线人泄露而责怪他
maybe blamed him for the CI leak.
-也许吧  -继续调查弹道
- Maybe. - Follow up with Ballistics.
我搜查了小哥住处的所有证据
I was going over the evidence from Lil GG's place.
有一条他和犯罪现场
There's a text message between him
被击中的人的短信
and the guy who got shot at the scene--
也就是不愿和我们说话的詹姆斯·佩尔
James Pell, the guy who won't talk to us.
现在我们知道原因了
Well, now we know why.
把他给我带过来
Get his ass down here right now.
-凯文  你要去吗  -是的
- Kev, you wanna come? - Yep.
詹姆斯·佩尔
James Pell?
我们一直想和你聊聊来着
We've been trying to talk to you.
我跟其他警察说了  我的枪伤还是很痛
Like I told the other cops, I'm in pain from the shooting
我最近专注于恢复之中
and focused on my recovery.
你接受了15分钟治疗就走了
You were treated and released in 15 minutes.
我觉得世界纪录也就是十分钟
I believe the world's record is ten.
你能有多疼
How much pain could you be in?
我没什么好说的
I got nothing to say.
看来我们要聊聊你的朋友小哥了
Look we just wanna talk about your friend Lil GG.
我不认识叫这个名字的人
I don't know anybody by that name.
你今天早上还发过短信给他
You were texting him this morning
就在神学院发生枪击之前
right before that shoot-out at the seminary.
我要找律师
I want a lawyer.
马上
Now.
你聋了吗
You deaf?
我说我他妈的要找律师
I said I want a damn lawyer.
去吧
So go.
出去
Get out.
埃尔文  这是普莱斯议员
Alvin, this is Alderman Price.
我知道他是谁
Oh, I know who he is.
是的  很高兴再次见到你  奥林斯基警探
Yeah, nice to see you again, Detective Olinsky.
詹姆斯·佩尔在里面吗
Is James Pell in there?
不好意思  你是...
I'm sorry. You are...
他就是我跟你说的人
He's the guy I was telling you about.
在  他在里面
Yeah, he's back there.
-他被批捕了吗  -没有
- Has he been arrested? - Nope.
那我建议你放了他
Then I suggest you release him.
我听说你是一个政客
You know, I heard you were a politician.
但我不知道你还是律师
I didn't realize you were a lawyer too.
不用去法学院就能看出
You don't have to go to law school to see that
芝加哥警局又一次骚扰无辜良民
the Chicago PD is once again harassing an innocent man.
他可以走了
He's free to go.
谢谢你  警探
Oh, thank you, Detective, uh...
其实  是警长  博伊特
Actually, it's Sergeant. Voight.
博伊特  雷·普莱斯  幸会
Voight. Ray Price. Nice to meet you.
我知道你们小组因为
Now, I understand that your unit is under pressure
神学院发生的不幸事件压力很大
for the unfortunate incident that happened at the seminary.
-我深表同情  -嗯
- And I sympathize with that. - Mm.
但请不要骚扰
But do not harass
我选区内辛勤工作的人
the hardworking men and women of my ward.
还真是能说会道啊  雷
That is a hell of a speech, Ray.
真遗憾这里没有摄像机
It's too bad the cameras weren't rolling.
很快摄像机就会来了
Oh, they will be soon enough.
相信我
Trust me on that.
埃尔  你送这几位先生出去吧
Al, why don't you show these gentlemen back?
谢谢帮忙  警长
Thanks for your help, Sergeant.
好
Yeah.
这个人
This guy.
你们最近联系过霍斯特德吗
Hey, you guys talk to Halstead lately?
几小时之前  怎么了
A few hours ago. What's up?
照孩子们说的是  他在网上火了
Well, as the kids say, he is blowing up the Internet,
不是以正面形象
and not in a good way.
"杀童者还是一个种族主义者"
"Child killer is racist too."
种族主义  什么
Racist? What?
这里还有  "种族主义警察
Here's another: "Racist cop punched
无缘无故殴打非裔美国警察"
African American Cop for no reason."
不不不  那个人是在骚扰琳德赛
No, no, no, no, no, that guy was harassing Lindsay.
他给她发了一堆下流短信
He sent her a bunch of perverted texts.
这也太快了
That didn't take long.
"现在美国民权联盟和全国有色人种协进会
"The ACLU and NAACP are now demanding
要求芝加哥警局解雇霍斯特德
that Chicago PD fire Halstead."
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
牛肉就应该这样熏制
Now, that's how you smoke brisket.
谢谢你过来  汉克
Thanks for coming down, Hank.
-很好  -是的
- That's good. - Yeah.
有点卡津人的感觉啊
Has a little of that Cajun kick to it.
我今天不是故意
I didn't mean to be
跟你起冲突
so confrontational today.
但事实上  你和我
But the truth is, you and me,
我们是一个同一战线的
we're on the same team.
是吗  怎么说
Yeah, how do you figure that?
我们都很热爱这座城市
Well, we both love this city,
我们也愿意不顾一切地保护这里的市民
and we both would do anything to protect its citizens.
当然了  除非你是一个警察
Unless, of course, you're a cop
你意外开枪打中了一个孩子
and you accidentally shoot a kid.
你知道今天的各种头条吗
You know all those headlines today,
种族主义的罪名
accusations of racism?
我猜是你干的
See, I'm guessing that's you.
当然是
Sure is.
你知道  霍斯特德
You know, Halstead--
他看上去像是个好警察
you know, he seems like a good cop.
也是个好人
Good guy too.
管他呢  今天一整天
Hell, I had five people
我找了五个人挖他的底
digging in his ass all day.
他们唯一能发现的黑料就是
The only negative thing they could find was
他跟某个腐败的黑警打过架
a fistfight he had with some degenerate black cop.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
这个是在这里做的  五英里之外
This is made right here, five miles away.
黑人出资  黑人所有
Black owned, black financed.
波旁威士忌也特别棒
Bourbon is damn good too.
百分之百玉米酿造  所以才会这么甜
100% corn. That's why it's so sweet.
所以我们过来是为了喝波旁吗
So we come down here to drink bourbon?
不是
No.
我们过来是为了解决问题
We came here to solve the problem--
-你我之间的问题  -好吧
- you and me. - Okay.
必须有人为那个小姑娘付出代价
Somebody has to pay for that little girl.
还有其他的小男孩小姑娘
And all the other little boys and girls
以及各种警察乱开枪
and the police shootings and the ass whuppings.
这个城市比以前更需要找人背黑锅
More than ever, this city needs someone to blame,
而那个人就是一个年轻帅气的白人警察
and that person is a young, good-looking white cop
叫杰·霍斯特德
named Jay Halstead.
你想让我帮忙吗
And you want me to help?
不
No.
我想让你不要碍事
I want you to get the hell out of the way.
确实好喝
That really is good.
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
放轻松  别紧张
Easy. Just relax.
哥们  你在干什...
Man, what the hell are you--
别紧张  我是以朋友的身份来的
Just relax. I'm here as a friend.
-我朋友够多了  -是的
- I got enough friends. - Yeah.
但没人可以洗脱你的谋杀罪
Well, none that can get you out from under a murder rap.
谋杀罪
A murder rap?
我们怀疑你卷入了
You were lookout in a gun deal
两名无辜平民被杀的枪战案件
where two innocent people were killed.
这可是谋杀重罪  朋友
That's felony murder, my man.
作为你的朋友
As a friend,
我可以说服州检察官
I can convince the state's attorney
以较轻的罪名起诉你
to charge you with a lesser crime.
你们没有足够的证据
You don't have enough
起诉我在现场
to charge me with jaywalking.
还没有
Well, not yet.
但我们会找到的
But we will.
如果你帮我  我也会帮你
Look, you help me, I'll return the favor.
如果你不肯
If you don't,
我会说服州检察官
I'll convince the state's attorney
你是主谋
you're the mastermind, mm.
对  你应该为那女士和小姑娘
Yeah, you're the one responsible for the murder
之死负责
of that woman and the little girl.
你想要什么
What do you need?
水坑烧烤
好  再来一次  纯属娱乐
All right, one more time, just for fun.
死的两个骑手是安东尼·乔纳斯和麦克·斯考拉
The two dead bikers are Anthony Jonas and Mike Scola,
我的弟弟  我们来自噶里
my younger brother, and we're from Gary.
我们买卖冰毒和枪支
We deal meth and guns.
你和我在布兰奇维尔相识
You and I met in Branchville.
你是因为持械抢劫进去过
You were in for armed robbery.
我是因为故意伤害
I was doing time for aggravated assault.
我们来这...
And we're here...
是为了拿前几天所发生的事的补偿
To get compensated for what happened the other day.
-好的  -一定很有趣
- All right. - This is gonna be fun.
听着  马克思
Listen, Marcus.
我没了价值4万美元的枪
I lost $40,000 worth of guns,
一个叫托尼·乔纳斯的朋友  和我的小弟麦克
a friend named Tony Jonas, and my little brother Mike.
那场枪战真的让我们损失惨重
That shoot-out really cost us.
抱歉  兄弟  但是枪的事我一点也不知道
Sorry, bro, but I don't know anything about no guns.
真的吗
Really?
因为我兄弟说他是直接和你
'Cause my brother said he was dealing
还有一个叫小哥的朋友交易的
directly with you and a friend named Lil GG.
你一定是我和别人弄混了
You must got me confused with someone else.
如果你要撒谎  马克思
If you're gonna lie, Marcus,
你为什么还要和我们见面
why did you even take the meeting?
因为我想做点新生意
'Cause I wanna do some new business.
我需要手枪
I need heaters.
所以我们忘掉过去的不愉快
So why don't we leave the past in the past
聊聊现在吧
and we just talk about the present?
因为我兄弟佩尔说你做好做生意的准备了
'Cause my man Pell said you ready to deal.
还没有
Not yet.
我们还有正事要做
We still got business to do.
我昨天和你的一个兄弟聊了聊
I rapped with one of your boys yesterday.
一个叫哈洛德的兄弟
A dude named Harold.
说你有很多枪要卖给我
Said you got a lot of guns to sell me.
-你知道哈洛德吗  -我知道我来这是来谈...
- You know Harold? - I know I'm here to talk--
你知不知道哈洛德  知道还是不知道  兄弟
Do you know Harold, yes or no, bro?
我的小弟被杀
My little brother was killed
就是因为你们之中有人泄密
because you got a leak in your crew.
你想试探我是不是不是条子
You're gonna question whether I'm legit,
就随便编了个叫哈洛德的人来试探我吗
make up some dude named Harold?
想要耍我  抓我个现行
Try to play me, catch me alive?
你在看什么  傻佬
What you looking at, cuz?
你他妈和谁说话呢  二货
Who the hell you talking to, fam?
我们正在聊正事  你...
Talking business. Why don't you--
没人和你这个白鬼说话
Wasn't nobody talking to your white ass,
-所以你闭上你的嘴吧  -白鬼
- so you can shut up. - My white ass?
-我在和这个小丑说话  -兄弟  你说谁是小丑
- I'm talking to this clown-- - Man, who you calling a clown?
你们认真的吗  为什么是我走
Are you serious? Why I gotta go?
我什么都没...
I ain't even do--
好了  我走了  我走了
Okay, I'm outside. I'm outside.
你给老子在外面等着
I'll see you there!
-现在  -好了  冷静
- Right here. - You're good. Calm down.
-你没事了吧  没事了吧  -没事了
- You good? You good? - Yeah.
我只是不喜欢有人打扰我们谈生意
I just don't like when people interfere with business,
你懂我的意思吧
you know what I mean?
没事的  没事的  兄弟
It's all good. It's okay, man.
我懂
I understand.
那我们怎么做呢
So how we gonna do this?
是用容易的方法还是相反的方法
Easy way or the other way?
听着
Hey, look.
关于你弟弟和另一个兄弟的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your brother and the other dude,
但是枪和钱的事我一点都不知道
but I don't know anything about no guns and no money.
我能做到的最大限度就是给你们一千美元
The best thing I can do is just offer $1,000.
两条命
For two lives
和四万的货
and 40 grand worth of merchandise?
听着
Hey, look.
对于我来说也很疯狂
It was crazy for me too.
我几乎丢了命
I almost lost my life.
条子来了  到处都是子弹
Cops rolled up. Bullets started flying.
场面一团混乱
The whole thing was just a mess.
谢谢你的诚实  马克思
I appreciate your honesty, Marcus.
就一千好了
$1,000 it is.
干得漂亮  兄弟
Great job, bro.
谢了  窃听情况还好吧
Thanks, the wire good?
非常好
Perfect.
-好久不见  -是啊
- It's been a while. - Yeah.
-谢谢帮忙  -应该的
- Thanks for helping out. - Sure thing.
也许我应该继续
You know, maybe I should stick around
帮你们抓这个混蛋
and help you bust this punk too.
我是借调的  应该好好利用利用  物有所值
I'm on loan. Might as well get your money's worth.
好主意
Sounds great.
海莉·厄普顿
Hailey Upton.
幸会  久仰大名啊
Hey, nice to meet you. I've heard a lot about you.
刚刚很抱歉  兄弟
Sorry about that, man.
不用  没事的  我明白
No, it's okay. I get it.
不不不  他那会都掏枪了
No, no, no, he was reaching for his gun.
-你做的是对的  -好了  听着
- No, it was the right move. - All right, listen up.
首先我们去申请逮捕令  然后我们去抓马克思
First we get a warrant. Then we grab Marcus.
走吧
Let's go.
干得漂亮
Good job.
-我去  -好了  起来
- Come on. - Come on, get up.
-你不想那么做的  -走
- You don't wanna do that. - Let's go.
拜托  你们除了查我房
Come on, you ain't got nothing
就无事可做了吗
better to do than running in my crib?
-我去  -别动  别动  别动
- Come on. - Hey, hey, hey.
你被捕了  哥们  闭上你的嘴
You're under arrest, man. Shut your ass up.
该死  兄弟
Damn, bro.
过得如何啊  马克思
Hey, how you doing, Marcus?
兄弟
Bro.
不要那样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
这是什么
What's this?
天啊
Oh, my goodness.
你在哪弄成这样的  玩马球吗
Where'd you get that, playing polo?
-我要律师  -律师
- Lawyer. - Lawyer?
-把他弄起来  -我要律师
- Stand him up. - I need my lawyer.
说实话  你很幸运
Truth is, you're lucky.
因为如果你没有那个枪伤的话
'Cause if you didn't have that bullet wound,
我会亲自给你一枪
I was gonna shoot you myself.
贯穿伤  在左腹部下面点
Through and through. Lower left side of the abdomen.
就像霍斯特德所说
Just like Halstead said.
所以他是对的
So he's right.
关于射中马克思·凯利的事
About shooting Marcus Kelly, anyway.
但这也没让警察脸上有光
Doesn't make it good police work.
日托中心有5个孩子  15英尺...
There were five children in the day care center, 15 feet--
我们真的要讨论那个
Are we really still talking about
非法的日托中心吗  先生
that illegal day care center, sir?
一个小女孩死了
A little girl is dead.
15发点45口径的子弹射向霍斯特德
15 .45-caliber rounds were fired in Halstead's direction.
一个女的  一个离他
A woman--a woman standing
20英尺的女的被杀了
20 feet away from him was killed.
如果你在警察学院教学生
If you're teaching a class at the academy
如何应对这种情况  你会说
on how to handle this situation, you'd say,
"按霍斯特德的做法做"
"Do it the way Halstead did it."
这个案子我承受了很大的压力  汉克
There's a lot of pressure on this one, Hank--
来自高层的压力
from up high.
我明白那种感受
Yeah, I'm sort of getting that feeling.
你想你已经知道我们逮捕了马克思·凯利
I imagine you already heard we arrested Marcus Kelly.
我们有他谈论那笔枪支交易的录音
Yeah, got him on tape talking about the gun deal.
还找到了凶器
Found the murder weapon too.
我知道了
Yeah, I read about that.
你知道了
You read about it?
对啊  我就知道他肯定会直接告诉你的
Yeah, I felt sure he would have called you directly.
你说什么
Excuse me?
在他的手机上发现的
Yeah, found this on his phone.
我一点都不惊讶
Doesn't surprise me.
我认识他很多年了
I've known him for years.
他的帮派出资资助我的竞选
His gang donates to my campaign.
不过你已经知道了吧
But, uh, you already know that, huh?
你已经跟马克思聊过我
You already talked to Marcus about me,
-聊过我们的关系了  -没错
- our relationship. - Yes, I did.
说实话  我别无选择
Truth is, I don't have a choice.
有钱的白人不会往这场战争中投钱
Rich white folks aren't pouring cash into this war.
所以我需要做需要之事
So I need to do what I need to do
来救这里那些想得到拯救的人
to save the people around here who want to be saved.
都只是生意的一部分
It's just a part of doing business.
南部老鹰帮为这里捐赠了20万
The Southside Hawks donated $200 grand to this place.
-是吗  -是的
- Really? Wow. - Yeah.
我们说话这会儿
It's a place where, as we speak,
有孩子在这里打篮球  读书
kids are playing basketball, learning how to read,
学使用电脑
using the computers.
没有邪恶的帮派
Without the big, bad, evil gang,
这里不会建起来
this doesn't get built.
我懂
I get it.
真的  我懂
I really do. I get it.
但说实话
But I'll tell you what.
大部分人不懂
Most people won't.
这样的照片
I mean, a picture like this--
这种东西泄露出去  你跟一个杀人犯
this kind of thing gets out, I mean, arm in arm
跟一个杀孩子的人这么亲密
with a murderer, child killer?
这种事大家永远不会忘
I mean, it's the kind of thing people don't forget.
这会让你很难做生意
Make it real hard for you to do business,
很难帮你选区的人
to help the people of your ward.
你想怎么做
What's your proposal?
放过霍斯特德
Just back off Halstead.
没问题
I can do that,
如果你放过佩尔
if you back off Pell.
放哨的佩尔
Pell, the lookout?
他不止如此
He's more than that.
他是整个团伙的大脑人物
He's the brains of the whole crew.
他不贩毒  不开枪杀人
He doesn't deal drugs, shoot people.
他的重点是赚钱
He focuses on making money.
所以我需要他出来
So I need him out there on the street
确保资金顺利周转
making sure that the cash flow continues.
马克思呢
And Marcus?
随你处置
Bury his ass.
合作愉快
Alderman.
Hank.
摩根·威廉姆斯的枉死
Morgan Williams' senseless death
让全城人民陷入
has caused this city great distress
无比的悲痛
and pain.
结果  我们去努力
And as a result, we've gone to great lengths
找人负责
to find someone to blame,
找人憎恨
someone to hate.
此前没人比我更憎恨
And no one has wanted to hate Detective Halstead
霍斯特德警探
more than me.
但我对
But the more I learned
那天早上发生的事越了解
about what actually transpired that morning,
越是确信霍斯特德警探
the more I'm convinced Detective Halstead
没做错什么
did nothing wrong.
事实上  他的行为
In fact, his actions
救了好几个人
saved several lives--
好几个黑人
several black lives.
-借过  -我们真的...
- Excuse me. - We really want to...
休想
Nice try.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
回见  汉克
I'll see you around, Hank.
抱歉  我尽快过来了
Sorry, I got here as fast as I could.
结束了吗
It's over?
对  刚结束了
Yeah, just ended.
情况如何
How'd it go?
不错  其实很不错
It was good. Really good, actually.
价格很公道
Price was very gracious.
我也不知道到底怎么变成这样了  但是
I'm not really sure what prompted all this, but--
就当我答应了
Hey, take yes for an answer.
如果你有任何需要  尽管找我
If there's anything you need, please let me know.
我会没事的
I'll be okay eventually.
我就只需要弄明白这一切
I think I just gotta make sense of all of it.
是很艰难
Yeah. It's tough.
相信我
Trust me.
你...
Have you...
对
Yeah.
虽然情况不同  不过
Different circumstances, but...
跟摩根的妈妈谈过了吗
Talk to Morgan's mother yet?
没有  我觉得我没准备好
No. I don't think I'm ready.
你永远不会准备好
Oh, man. You're never gonna be ready.
去做就行了
You just have to do it.
责任不在霍斯特德警探...
Detective Halstead is not the man to blame...
听上去是好消息
Sounds like good news.
-我们不该恨他  -是啊
- Not the man to hate. - Yeah, yeah.
不过让人深思
Makes you think, though.
霍斯特德只是在尽职做自己的工作
I mean, Halstead's just doing his job,
天啊  他差点被杀死了
he almost gets killed, for God sakes,
可他们却想尽办法让他身败名裂
and they try their best to throw him under the bus.
当警察真难
It's a tough time to be a cop.
至少在芝加哥是如此
In Chicago, anyway.
对  为此我要喝一杯
Yeah, I'll drink to that.
等一下
Wait, no.
我们还是为别的喝这杯吧
I say we drink to something else instead.
同意  敬霍斯特德
I agree. To Halstead.
敬霍斯特德
To Halstead.
金  你还想喝一瓶吗
Kim, you want another beer?
不喝了
No, I'm good.
晚点我们...
Maybe later, we could, uh--
不
No.
真的不是个好主意
It's just not a good idea.
我从没说过是
Well, I never said it was a good idea.
我认识了个人
I met someone.
好事
That's great.
你真的不要再来一瓶了吗
You--you sure you don't want another beer?
不了
I'm good.
好  晚安
All right. Have a good night.
上次我们吃饭时  你说很高兴
The last time we had dinner, you said you weren't too happy
在州检察官办公室工作
over at the state's attorney's office.
那种长期调查有点无聊
Those long-tail investigations get a little boring.
如果你想找点刺激
Well, if you're looking for a little more excitement,
随时欢迎你回来
you're welcome back in the unit full-time.
虽然可能需要处理点事
Might have to juggle a few things,
不过听上去是个好主意
but that sounds great.
我找到了摩根的项链
I found Morgan's necklace.
我想给你
I wanted you to have it.
真的对不起
I'm very sorry.